<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>syndesis</title>
    <link>https://syndesis.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on syndesis</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 May 2017 15:58:18 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://syndesis.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Quickstart</title>
      <link>https://syndesis.io/quickstart/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2017 15:58:18 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://syndesis.io/quickstart/</guid>
      <description>We aim to make it as simple as possible for users to try out Syndesis. If you want to try out locally on your laptop, follow the Using Minishift instructions.
Using Minishift Minishift is a tool that helps you run OpenShift locally by running a single-node OpenShift cluster inside a VM locally. With Minishift you can easily try out Syndesis without requiring a &amp;ldquo;real&amp;rdquo; cluster or servers, a laptop will suffice.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Announcing Syndesis</title>
      <link>https://syndesis.io/blog/syndesis-release-1.0.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2017 16:42:50 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://syndesis.io/blog/syndesis-release-1.0.0/</guid>
      <description>The Integration Platform That’s For Everyone - No Coding Required. Best of All? Syndesis runs in the cloud or on-premise, on OpenShift or Kubernetes. The week before Red Hat Summit is always crazy, seemingly endless demo recordings, and lots of blood, sweat, and tears. So many tears. Even more so when your project is going to have it&amp;rsquo;s first public airing. And so our team is ecstatic to announce the release of Syndesis, a game-changing data integration platform that can be run in the cloud, requires no code whatsoever (but can be extended, should you be so inclined), and, in typical Red Hat fashion, is completely open source.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://syndesis.io/roadmap/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://syndesis.io/roadmap/</guid>
      <description>Roadmap Current Sprint: 12 Ends: May 12, 2017 (Fri)
Preview Release Requirements &amp;amp; Stories
JIRA Narrative
JIRA Issues for Keynote</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://syndesis.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://syndesis.io/about/</guid>
      <description>Syndesis is a flexible, customizable platform that provides core integration capabilities as a service. It can be run on the cloud or on premises with OpenShift or Kubernetes, is fully extensible and, best of all, is open source.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact Us</title>
      <link>https://syndesis.io/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://syndesis.io/contact/</guid>
      <description>A list of Syndesis points of contact and core contributors. This is likely not 100% up-to-date or correct, so feel free to correct as necessary. Also, please note that many of these hardworking folk have cross-collaborated (both UI and API, backend and API, etc).
 Fuse Engineering Manager: Aileen Cunningham Product Manager: Keith Babo Architect &amp;amp; Technical Lead: Jimmi Dyson Back-End: Claus Ibsen Hiram Chirino, Ioannis Cannellos, Kurt Stam, Luca Burgazzoli, Roland Huß, Zoran Revgart Front-End: Stan Lewis, Rachel Yordán Data Mapper: Matt Pavlovich (Media Driver) QE: David Simansky, Josef Ludvicek Support: Tova Cohen, Nichola Moore UXD: Catherine Robson, SJ Cox, Dongni Wang  Thanks to everyone for your continued hard work!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FAQ</title>
      <link>https://syndesis.io/faq/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://syndesis.io/faq/</guid>
      <description>Syndesis looks awesome. Who is it for? Anyone that wants to integrate services. Syndesis includes a swish UI that enables the user to design integration flows and manage them from their browser.
No coding required&amp;hellip; Unless you really want to and then Syndesis allows you to dive into the code, develop your own connectors (if one doesn&amp;rsquo;t already exist), or hack on the integration definition directly.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>